mechanicalbuzz.com 2015-05-15

# Privacy Policy

This blog is related to mechanical theories,machines,mechanisms and any personal information of our visitor provide to us including Name,e-mail address will not displayed and didn't share to any other individuals. Mechanicalbuzz respects the information provided by visitor to us. And the privacy of our visitors is extremely importance to Mechanicalbuzz team.

**Security**

Mechanicalbuzz team respects the information of blog readers.The security of blog readers is important to us. Mechanicalbuzz team strive to protect the Personal Information of our blog readers. we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Mechanicalbuzz does not use cookies to collect personal infomation of blog readers.

**Comments**

We love to hear from our blog readers in the form of comments. Your comments encourage our team and helps us to rectify the information. You can comment on our blog posts and talk to us.To comment on our blog post you need to provide e-mail Id as to notify you about the replay to your comment.

**External Links**

Mechanicalbuzz may contain links to other sites these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Mechanicalbuzz has not responsibility for the content, privacy policies of any third party sites.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Mechanicalbuzz updates Privacy Policy from time to time.We will notify you of any changes in the blog with new privacy policy statements on the site.

**Contact us**

If you have any quires about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
